freshpair.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy & Security at Freshpair.com

You're safe with us. At Freshpair, we take the protection of your privacy seriously. We use the information we collect strictly to improve the quality of your shopping experience and we never rent, trade, or sell your private information to others. We also use the highest encryption standards available through an SSL certification.

## privacy policy

Freshpair's Privacy Policy provides you with the information and policies regarding our information collection processes, how we use the information we collect, and our privacy protection assurance. By using the Freshpair site, you agree to the conditions of this privacy policy.

  * The information we collect
  * How we use and share the personal information we collect
  * Communications from Freshpair
  * Changes to Privacy Policy
  * Questions or comments

### The information we collect

Each time a user visits Freshpair, certain information is collected. That information below is specific to your visit and whether you browse, shop or register. Depending on those actions, different unique information is gathered. The information below details the types of information we collect, how it is gathered and what is done with it.

### IP address, cookies, pixel tags, and gifs: non-identifying Information

Part of each visit to Freshpair is registered through an IP address that may help us diagnose issues with our servers and correct errors. Your IP address also allows us to gather broad, non-personal demographics that help us to analyze traffic patterns and how our site is browsed.

Cookies allow you to use the shopping cart on our site. Without cookies one cannot order from Freshpair online. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers transferred from our site to your computer so that we may identify you when you visit. These files also provide non-personally identifiable browsing and purchasing information which Freshpair and its third-party vendors use to serve you more efficiently.

Most computers are pre-set to accept cookies. You can opt to have your computer warn you each time cookies are being selected or you can opt to deny cookies. If you refuse the acceptance of cookies on your computer, you will not be able to complete an online order with us.

In order to monitor the success and usage of our email marketing campaigns, Freshpair may implement 'message format' or 'message open' sensing technology. These technologies require pixel tags or clear Gifs which are unseen to the user, but send the appropriate information to our tracking system. This information allows us to identify if your email accepts HTML or text only emails so that we may send you the appropriate format.

### Registration and order information

Freshpair uses a registration process and order form so that you can purchase online, request information and receive service from us. Your personal contact information (i.e. name, email address, telephone number, mailing address, etc.) is used to send you your order and to fulfill marketing programs.

Credit card information is completely secure and protected and collected for the sole purpose of billing you for your purchase.

Users may browse our products and information without registering. Registration is optional and only required to shop online.

### How we use and share the information we collect

Freshpair is proud to inform you that we do not sell or share your personal information or email. Your information is only used to complete your order and for marketing purposes, if you have opted for this feature.

Should you select the optional opportunity to receive emails from us about current offers and incentives, we will also use your email for this purpose. If you have not selected this option, you will not receive promotional emails.

If you have opted to receive promotional email, you may choose to remove this feature from your account at any time and the emails will be stopped.

Your contact information may also be used should we ever need to contact you regarding your order.

Gift certificates and gifts also require that certain information is sent to third parties. This information receives the same courtesy detailed above for our customers.

### Communications from Freshpair

Freshpair offers many modes of communication to our customers. Freshpair also reserves the right to communicate with our registered users regarding their order should the need arise.

### Communication regarding transaction and account maintenance

Freshpair communications include order confirmations, order updates, problems with orders, delivery issues (as needed), and management of accounts (should issues arise).

### HTML emails and marketing

Freshpair offers our users an email option that allows us to communicate with you regarding sales, incentives, new products, and other offers. If you receive these emails, you may opt at any time to remove yourself from this mailing list. If you do not receive emails, you may add yourself to this feature in your account management area.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

Freshpair's privacy policy was last updated on August 2, 2012. Freshpair reserves the right to amend or append this policy at any time by posting those revisions on your site. Any changes will only affect information collected after this post date unless otherwise stated.

### Questions or comments

Freshpair invites you to communicate with us should you have a question or would like to voice a concern regarding our privacy or security policies. Please email us at [info@freshpair.com](mailto:info@freshpair.com) and a customer service associate will respond to you in a timely manner. You may also call us at (347) 472-1242 

## security policy

  * Protecting Your Information
  * Password Security
  * Safe Shopping Guarantee
  * Alternate Shopping Options
  * Changes to Security

### Protecting your information

At Freshpair, your security is our first priority. We are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers and using the information responsibly and only for the purposes defined in our registration process. Our state of the art software and ensures that information shared with Freshpair is secure and private.

We guarantee that every transaction you make at Freshpair will be safe. When you shop online with us, you will join a community of customers pleased with our service.

Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) is among the best available for secure online transactions. We exceed all industry standards in securing transactions, encrypting all credit card information, name, address and other personal info so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet. These measures provide strong security to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of this information.

### Password security

As an additional element of our security efforts, Freshpair requires you to create and use a customer username and password. This information is required to sign in and shop online with us. We strongly recommend that users select a password that is difficult to guess (in other words, do not use your name, birth date, or other familiar phrases). We suggest you keep this information private and not leave it accessible to others. If you share an office or work-space, do not leave your password available in a document or other public arena.

If you happen to forget your password, please click the link entitled [Forgot Password](https://secure.freshpair.com/forgot_password.php) and follow the instructions. Our Customer Care team will ensure you receive a note to your registered email address. If you would like to change your password, simply enter [My Account](https://secure.freshpair.com/account.php) and follow the prompts to change your information.

### Safe shopping guarantee

Federal law ensures that a credit card user will not be liable for charges in excess of $50.00 that result from the unauthorized use of that card. Debit cards have similar protections. Freshpair requires users to comply with credit card rules and regulations. Please take the time to review your cardholder policy for more details on this subject.

Should you be charged a fee by your credit card company for the illegal use of your card with your purchase from Freshpair, we will reimburse you up to $50 for that penalty.

### Alternate shopping options

Freshpair stands behind its commitment to secure online shopping. However, if you are still uncomfortable shopping online, we invite you to call our friendly customer care center. Our representatives will be happy to take your order over the phone.

### Changes to security

Freshpair's security policy was last updated on August 2, 2012. Freshpair reserves the right to amend or append this policy at any time by posting those revisions on your site. Any changes will only affect information collected after this post date unless otherwise stated.

back to top
